foreign
among the prophets
this is repeated in Quran because
they're not like distinctions amongst
any prophets this is why in this mosque
we don't want to say that because
foreign
you heard this
and you heard this message on them so I
mean you know what are you going to do
get all involved with the with the radio
or the name of the radio or are you
going to listen to what this video is
saying
but I could mention some other names
with you know Kenwood you know you could
say whatever oh it is totally be solving
or it's always a leaders that counts and
just ignore it what comes out from the
you know it's like
it's like a receiving a message it's
like receiving something on the radio
and I think is it very direct
analogy if you understood the process of
Revelation it said like there's an
intermediary
foreign
thank you
you're describing for example Ibrahim
Prophet Ibrahim
he wasn't either worshiping Community he
did not go to school and
but he met because we are all born with
a domestic
thank you
no
yes
172.
so all those people to described are in
an isolated
or whatever the Olympic world records of
God is the Lord and it doesn't matter
who teaches them what
they have the knowledge inside them
instinctively
there is no excuse
me
doesn't matter the route but the only
reason people went there and taught in
Christianity and the accepted it is that
the cause they deserve that this is what
they actually believe
and if there are individuals in that
Community who believe in God alone will
actually make it through Christianity
they will reject the sonship of Jesus to
God or God of Jesus being God or the
Trinity and they will believe in God
alone
Abraham is a very good example
okay
and drink our tea and go home and they
shall not come here for a great steak
dinner for our souls at six o'clock in
the morning
foreign
to the max
[Music]